<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DeogharCity</string>
    <string name="baidyanathdham_deoghar">Baidyanathdham Deoghar</string>
    <string name="picoftemple">picOfTemple</string>
    <string name="aboutDeoghar">\n\nDeoghar is a holy city beside the Mayurakshi River, in the east Indian state of Jharkhand.\n
        The ancient Baba Baidyanath Temple complex is a significant Hindu pilgrimage site. Nearby, Shiv Ganga is a sacred pool where devotees of Shiva bathe.\n There is a shrine to Krishna in the ornate, stone-carved Naulakha Mandir temple.\n Northeast of town, Harila Jori is the site of a whitewashed Shiva temple and a sacred water tank.
    Deoghar is the main city of the Deoghar \nDistrict in the Santhal Parganas division of the state of Jharkhand, India. It is an important Hindu pilgrimage centre with the Baidyanath Temple being one of the twelve Shiva Jyothirlingas in India and one of the 51 Shakti Peethas in India. \nIt is situated 150 km from region’s largest city Bhagalpur. Deoghar was earlier part of Dumka District. It is the 5th largest city of Jharkhand.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="click_here">click here</string>
    <string name="culture">Culture
People \n
Deoghar is the cultural capital of Jharkhand, it has a large mix of different cultures and people. There is a significant percentage of people who are Bengalis, Biharis and locals. There are also significant Gujarati, Punjabi and Tamil, Malayali, Telugu, Marwari Rajasthani communities who have been living in Deoghar for a long time.This diversity is also mirrored in the fact that there are a large number of languages spoken here.
\n
Festival
The major and most celebrated fairs and festivals include Dipawali, Holi, Chhath, Dussehra or Durga Puja, Ramanavami, Karma, Sarhul, Tusu, Eid ,Sarsawati Puja, Makar Sankranti, Jitiya etc. Due to presence of industries and mining activities Viskwakarma Puja is also one of the important festivals. Makar Sankranti fair also attracts lots of people.
\n
Cuisine\n
Deoghar has a variety of foods and cuisines. The most known and common cuisine that are practically prepared in every household includes Roti (Chapati) or Phulka , Rice or Bhat, Dal, Sabzi and last but definitely not the least, Achar or Pickle. Dhuska and Vada is famous local fast food. Salty Dhuska ingredients are rice and urad dal. </string>
</resources>